Who's kicking me out? I'm carrying a Jiang heir
That's your grandson! Would you let him be homeless?
Stop pretending. You're too old
to even get pregnant
We're in a hospital, how could I lie?
You... my son begged for years
I'm done for, but the child is the Jiang family's only heir
In my past life, my husband and mother-in-law
betrayed me and got me killed
This life, I'll make your whole family pay in blood
Come wash my feet later
Zhang Guifang, don't push it! My precious son says
he wants grandma to serve him herself. If she doesn't do it right
he won't come out. Sit in there and wait, see who panics
With old Zhang... Honey, honey, calm down!
Careful with the baby in her belly! If it weren't
for the Jiang heir she's carrying,
I'd have thrown you out long ago!
Something's wrong. The way Jiang Chenggao
looked... not at a daughter-in-law
Ow!
Chen Gang, be gentle! I'm carrying
your heir... don't press on him!